[SIRENS WAILING]
♪♪
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[SOULFUL CHORAL MUSIC]
♪ Life is a mystery,
everyone must stand alone ♪
♪ I hear you call my name ♪
♪ And it feels like home ♪
[UPBEAT POP MUSIC]
♪ When you call my name
it's like a little prayer ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees,
I wanna take you there ♪
♪ In the midnight hour
I can feel your power ♪
♪ Just like a prayer you
know I'll take you there ♪
♪ I hear your voice, it's
like an angel sighing ♪
♪ I have no choice,
I hear your voice ♪
♪ Feels like flying ♪
♪ I close my eyes, oh
God I think I'm falling ♪
♪ Out of the sky,
I close my eyes ♪
♪ Heaven help me ♪
♪ When you call my name
it's like a little prayer ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees,
I wanna take you there ♪
♪ In the midnight hour
I can feel your power ♪
♪ Just like a prayer you
know I'll take you there ♪
♪ Like a child you whisper
softly to me ♪
♪ You're in control
just like a child ♪
♪ Now I'm dancing ♪
♪ It's like a dream, no
end and no beginning ♪
♪ You're here with me,
it's like a dream ♪
♪ Let the choir sing ♪
♪ When you call my name
it's like a little prayer ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees,
I wanna take you there ♪
♪ In the midnight hour
I can feel your power ♪
♪ Just like a prayer you
know I'll take you there ♪
♪ When you call my name
it's like a little prayer ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees,
I wanna take you there ♪
♪ In the midnight hour
I can feel your power ♪
♪ Just like a prayer you
know I'll take you there ♪
♪ Oh-Oh, oh-oh,
oh-Oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Life is a mystery,
everyone must stand alone ♪
♪ I hear you call my name ♪
♪ And it feels like home ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, your
voice can take me there ♪
♪ Just like a muse to
me, you are a mystery ♪
♪ Just like a dream, you
are not what you seem ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, no choice
your voice can take me there ♪
♪ Just like a prayer,
I'll take you there ♪
♪ It's like a dream to me ♪
-♪ Mm-hm ♪
-♪ Just like a prayer,
I'll take you there ♪
-♪ I'll take you there ♪
-♪ It's like a dream to me ♪
-♪ Oh yeah ♪
-♪ Just like a prayer,
I'll take you there ♪
-♪ I'll take you there ♪
-♪ It's like a dream to me ♪
♪ Oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Just like a prayer,
I'll take you there ♪
♪ Oh, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ It's like a dream to me ♪
♪ Oh, oh, whoa ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, your
voice can take me there ♪
♪ Just like a muse to
me, you are a mystery ♪
♪ Just like a dream, you
are not what you seem ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, no choice
your voice can take me there ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, your
voice can take me there ♪
♪ Just like a muse to
me, you are a mystery ♪
♪ Just like a dream, you
are not what you seem ♪
♪ Just like a prayer, no choice
your voice can take me there ♪
♪ Your voice can take me
there, like a prayer ♪
♪ It's like a prayer ♪
♪ Your voice can take me there ♪